"NETFLIX
オリジナルシリーズ"
♪〜
ORIGINAL WORK BY RENSUKE OSHIKIRI
〜♪
（台を叩く音）
（マーくん）ウガアアー
まるで歯が立たねぇー！
イライラをお前に歯を立てて
解消したる！
I was completely powerless!
I'll vent my anger by hitting you!
（男Ｂ）
なんスかなんスか もうっ！
What are you doing? Stop that!
（マーくん）
ラァアアアア
（男Ｂ）ちょっと！
やめて！
（マーくん）
ラァアアアア
（男Ｂ）ちょっと！
やめて！
大人がゲームで
癇癪(かんしゃく)を起こしてモメてる
Adults fighting over a video game?
（マーくん）
ラァアアアア
大人がゲームで
癇癪(かんしゃく)を起こしてモメてる
This place really is crude, right, Miyao?
やっぱりココは
下劣な場所だな 宮尾
Huh? What?
って アレ？
You're Ono, right?
大野さん…　でしょ？
You transferred to Minami Middle School
your third year?
（小春(こはる)）南中の３年の時
１組に転校してきた…
I-I've seen you here plenty of times,
（小春）
なっ何度かこういうトコで
見かけた事があるけど…
but this is the first time
we've talked like this.
こうして話すの…
初めてだね…
たっ対戦…
ものすごく強いんだよね
You're really amazing at
competitive games, right?
So good, even I've heard the rumors.
巷(ちまた)で噂に上がるくらい…
（小春）うう…
何言ってんだろ 私…
What am I saying?
I've heard she's extremely quiet.
ものすごく無口な子って
聞いてたから…
I have no idea what to talk about.
何話していいか
全然分からない…
This is the girl... Yaguchi...
この子が…　矢口君の…
（宮尾(みやお)）おーい
Hey!
Long time no see, Hidaka.
久しぶりだな 日高
あ…　あと大野さんも
Oh, and you too, Ono.
（宮尾）
ゲーセンとは無縁そうな
２人が一緒にいるから
It's surprising to see the pair of you
at an arcade.
ビックリして
話しかけちゃったよ！
It seemed so unlikely,
I had to say something.
Was the last time you saw each other
the middle school graduation?
２人とも
中学を卒業して以来か…？
Hidaka, I barely recognized you!
日高 見違えたな
Miyao...
（小春）
宮尾君… 気を使って
話しかけてくれたのかな
Did he come talk to us
'cause he cares for me?
Ah, and Ono's aura is as
mysterious as ever.
（宮尾）
おっ大野さんも相変わらず―
ミステリアスなオーラを
放ってるね
What the heck am I saying?
（宮尾）
何言ってんだ オレ
（小春）大野さん
Ono.
Since we're here,
can I ask you for a match?
せっかくだし
私とお手合わせ願えるかな…
いや…　やめた方がいいな
Well, I wouldn't if I were you.
（小春）え？　どうして？
Huh, how come?
The adults are having a fist-less and
kick-less fight of shirt-pulling.
（宮尾）大人達がパンチや
キックではなく―
服を引っ張り合う
ケンカをしている…
今日のところは諦めて
帰った方がいい
You should probably just give up
and head home for today.
You... you may be right.
そ…　そうだね
（土井）大野さん
Ono!
It's me, Doi! Have you forgotten?
僕だ！　土井だよ！
忘れたのかい？
一緒の小学校でキラキラ
光ってただろう？
We shined together in elementary school!
Doi...
土井…
今もホラ！
キラキラ光ってるだろう？
See, even now, I'm shining.
おおっ！
覚えててくれたのかい？
Oh, so you do remember me!
遊ぼう！　さっそく
遊ぼうじゃないか 大野さん
Let's play. Let's play something, Ono!
I'll go win some candy in your honor,
right now!
今から君のために甘いアメを
ＧＥＴしてあげるからさ！
（土井）ぐっ 取れねぇ
I can't do it.
100円で10個アメ買った方が
よかったかな…
Should I have just bought
10 candies for 100 yen?
Don't say that. That would've been boring.
そういうつまんないこと
言うなよな
Anyway, what happened to your medals
from earlier?
それよりさっきのメダルは
どうした？
I handed them in to the shop.
All 50,000.
（土井）
店に預けた…　５万枚…
If Yaguchi had gotten into
Joran High School,
（小春）
矢口君が
もし上蘭(じょうらん)に受かってたら
what kind of relationship would he and Ono
have had?
今頃―
大野さんとどういう関係に
なってたんだろう
あの矢口君にゲームを
ガマンさせるくらい―
She was able to get Yaguchi serious enough
to hold off on games.
本気にさせる人…
（ゴトン）
（土井）大野さん！
このゲームで僕が勝ったら
Ono, if I win this game,
come see a movie with me.
映画を観に行こう！
｢トイレの花子さん｣か
｢耳をすませば｣！
Either Hanako of the Toilet
or Whispers of the Heart.
What's with those choices?
（宮尾）なんだその２択
（ネットの音）
Crap!
（土井）クソっ クソ！
（土井）この絶妙な…
距離が…　難しい！
This distance makes it hard.
ねえ 大野さん
Hey, Ono.
Have you seen Yaguchi, lately?
（小春）最近 矢口君と
顔合わせてる？
（衝突音）
（晶）！
（宮尾･小春）うわっ！
It hit her square in the face.
モロに顔面イッたな オイ！
（宮尾）
今のが１人だったら―
If you had been alone, that could've been
so embarrassing.
恥ずかしくて
大惨事になってたぞ
でも…　ドジった時も
チャームだな 大野さんは…
But you're still charming,
even when you have a clumsy moment.
What are you saying, Miyao?
何言ってんのよ宮尾君
鼻とか歯が折れてたら
どーするの！
What if she'd broken her nose
or teeth or something?
（宮尾）ちょ…
本当に大丈夫か 大野さん…
Are you sure you're okay, Ono?
You're...
って…
moving on to Virtua Cop?
（宮尾）
｢バーチャコップ｣を
やるのかい？
なんかフラフラしてるし…
今日はもう帰った方が…
Um, you seem kind of dazed,
Maybe you should head home for today.
（コイン投入音）
I'll play with you.
（小春）私も一緒にやる
Oh! Two beautiful girls cooperating
in a shooting game?
（宮尾）えっ？
（土井）おお！
（土井）麗しき女子の
共同銃撃戦！　見ものだな…
A sight to behold.
This is crazy. This is crazy, Haruo!
（宮尾）えらいこっちゃ…
えらいこっちゃやで 春雄！
（ゲーム音）
（小春）あ！　スゴイ
Oh, wow.
It takes me two or three shots
to take down an enemy
敵を１人倒すのに
私が２〜３発に対して―
while Ono kills them all with one.
大野さんは確実に１発で
仕留めてる…
So calm and composed,
with no wasted movement.
冷静沈着でムダがなく
手際がよくて
Such dexterity.
She's a little hard to approach,
ちょっととっつきにくい
ところがあるけど
本当に綺麗(きれい)…
でもどこか陰があるような…
but she's so beautiful.
But she seems to have a dark side too.
I... want to know what
she's really thinking.
私 この人の本音が
知りたい…！
Ono...
大野さん
How do you feel about Yaguchi?
（小春）矢口君のこと
どう思ってるの？
（土井）おおっと！
Oh, no!
大野さんが一般人を
誤殺してしまったぞ！
Ono shot a civilian!
Since being rejected
by Joran High School,
上蘭高校に落ちてから―
矢口君 引け目を
感じてるみたいなの
Yaguchi has had an inferiority complex.
Toward you.
大野さんに対して…
（土井）おおっと！　また！
Oh, no! Not again!
何を話してるんだ 二人は…
I wonder what they're talking about!
I think he's distanced himself
from arcades,
しばらくゲーセンからも
足が遠のいていたのも
大野さんと会うのを
怖がってたからだと思うの…
because he was afraid of facing you.
He's always on the lookout and on edge
when he comes here.
ここに来るといつも
キョロキョロしたり
おどおどしたり…
（小春）ねぇ
Hey...
tell me how you really feel.
大野さんの
本当の気持ちを教えて
Seeing how Yaguchi is now,
I feel so sorry for him.
今の矢口君を見てると
かわいそうで仕方ないの
If you're not concerned for him...
もし大野さんが
矢口君に対して関心がなく
If you don't feel anything,
何も感じてないのであれば…
then I'll...
（小春）私が矢口君に…
あっ…
（射撃音）
（ゲーム音声）
うおっ…
あ…
すごいな 大野さん！
You're amazing, Ono!
大野さんがこんなにゲームが
上手だったなんて驚きさぁ！
I can't believe you're so good at games!
I'm seriously no match at all.
（小春）ホント…
まるで敵わない…
But I wonder how I'd fare
if it were a fighting game.
でも対戦格闘ゲームだったら
どんな勝負に…
W-Well, until we meet again.
（宮尾）じゃ…
じゃあまた会えたら
大野さんも気をつけて
帰って…
Go home safely, Ono.
（土井）ハッハッハッ
気をつけたまえー
（宮尾）
ふぅ…　穏便にすんだか
Things stayed amicable, thank goodness.
（宮尾）
ふぅ…　穏便にすんだか
Why am I being so considerate, Haruo?
（宮尾）
なんで俺がこんなに
気を使ってるんだ 春雄君…
What am I doing?
（小春）
私何やってんだろ
初めて話す子に…
I spoke to her for the first time,
しかもゲームプレイ中に
あんな事聞くなんて…
and I asked her all that mid-game, too.
Miss Akira.
（萌美(もえみ)）晶さん
It seems your awful habits
have continued into high school.
アナタの悪趣味は
高等学校に上がった今でも―
続いているようですね…
As the daughter of the Ono conglomerate,
大野財閥の
令嬢の身でありながら
あんな場所に出入りするなど
言語道断です
for you to frequent such a place
is inconceivable!
Um, Miss Goda. It may seem like
a distasteful hobby to you,
（爺や）
あ あの…　業田先生には
悪趣味に見えると思いますが
お嬢様にとっては
ささやかな楽しみ…
but to the Young Miss,
it's a modest past time.
It's her one interest that puts her
at ease.
（爺や）心の支え…
唯一の趣味でございます…
If she were to turn delinquent and spend
all her time there, that's one thing--
グレて不良娘になって
ゲーセンに入り浸るなら
ともかくですね…　あ…
（萌美）いえ 盛り場に
行く事自体が問題行動
No.
Going to degenerate places in itself
is unacceptable.
It's a symptom of delinquency.
グレる兆候とみます
（爺や）な ならば…
家庭用の据え置き機の購入を
T-Then consider buying her
a console for home--
What in the world are you talking about?
（萌美）何ですの それは
（爺や）プレステとか
サターンとか…
Like a PlayStation or Saturn,
or the upcoming  Virtual Boy!
今度発売する
バーチャルボーイとか…
ゲームのことなんて
まったく分かりません
I don't know a single thing about games!
先生！　バーチャルボーイ
買って差し上げましょうよ！
Ms. Goda, please let's buy
a Virtual Boy for her.
私も欲しいからぁ！
I want one, too!
We shall not.
（萌美）なりません
（爺や）
お願いします！　バーチャ…
Please!
-Please--
-Enough!
（萌美）うるさい！
（転がる音）
ローで持ってかれたか…
That low kick got the best of me.
大野家の指南役を
務めさせて頂くこの業田萌美
I, Moemi Goda, instructor
of the Ono family,
do not make compromises.
甘えや妥協は絶対許しません
I will watch over her closely
in her most vulnerable high school years.
高校生という子供達が
一番危うい時期を
しっかり管理させて頂きます
I have made your parents promise
not to give you even one yen.
（萌美）お母様方には―
１円たりとも金銭を
渡さないことを約束させます
I won't have you even playing the
ten-yen rock-paper-scissors game.
10円でできる―
ジャンケンマンすら
許しませんから
ちょっと知ってるじゃん…
So, you do know a bit...
Your curfew is 4 p.m.
門限は午後４時
学校からの直帰は厳守！
You must come straight home from school.
（爺や）
そっそれでは ご友人との
親交もままならなく…
She won't be able to build relationships
with her friends that way...
結構毛だらけ
猫灰だらけですわ
That's fine. Perfect.
Conversing with them at school
should be plenty.
ご友人との交流は
校内で十分…
Romantic relationships with boys
is out of the question.
（萌美）男子との交流…
恋愛なんてもってのほか
高校を卒業して一流大学に
入学して勉学に専念したのち
Once you've graduated and begun studying
at a top-class college,
決められた男性との結婚が
控えているのです
your parents will choose your husband.
That is the will of your father
and mother!
それが―
アナタのお父様とお母様の
御意思なのです！
（犬の鳴き声）
（ゲーム音）
（春雄）クックックッ…
この体勢で100面まで
クリアしたぞ
I've cleared 100 levels in this position.
初心に返る以上のことを
成した気分だぜ…
I feel like I've regained my roots
and then some.
（春雄）まあ…
感覚がおかしくなって
My senses are so messed up, it might
have an opposite effect on other games.
他のゲームに逆効果な
気がするがよしとしよう
Ah, well.
極め付けは同じクラスの
金持ちの小林君から借りた―
I borrowed this beauty, the Neo Geo CD
from Kobayashi, the rich kid in my class.
｢ネオジオＣＤ｣
これでいくらでも家庭内で
武者修行が可能になった
With this I can get as much
intensive training as I want at home.
What'll happen if I can practice endlessly
without worrying about money?
この俺が金銭を
気にしないで―
際限なく
練習したらどうなるか…
I'm sure I'll leave her dumbfounded with
my superhuman ability.
きっと度肝を抜く
超人的強さになって
日高も気絶するに
決まってらぁ〜
I'm sure Hidaka will faint from shock.
ふふふふ…
Achoo!
（なみえ）ハクション！
（鼻をすする音）
（春雄）
う〜ん　ふふふふ…
（犬の鳴き声）
んんん…
（猫の鳴き声）
なっ長い…！
It takes so long!
大野家令嬢としての使命を
まっとうすること…
As daughter of the Ono family,
you must take your duties seriously.
Accept it.
受け入れるのです
（萌美）
プライベートは皆無と
思いなさい…
You don't get to have a private life!
矢口君…
引け目を感じてるみたいなの
Yaguchi seems to have
an inferiority complex, toward you.
大野さんに対して…
Tell me, how you really feel?
（小春）
大野さんの本当の気持ちを
教えて…
（こらえ泣き）
JULY 1995
（セミの鳴き声）
（ゲーム音）
She's not here either.
（春雄）ここにもいねーか…
It's already been a week since I got
my feel and confidence back.
感覚と自信と取り戻してから
早１週間…
I've searched all the arcades
and candy shops I could think of,
思い当たる近所のゲーセンや
駄菓子屋を探しまくってるが
but I still haven't seen Ono.
いまだに大野の姿が
見当たらん…
I'm finally in the right mindset
to meet her,
せっかく面と向かえる
気になれたのに…
what's going on?
なんだってんだよ…
I'd always see her car parked outside
arcades before...
前はしょっちゅう
大野ん家の車が―
ゲーセン前で停まってるのを
見かけたのに…
（ゲーム音声）
きゃあ〜
MATCH OVER
A 21-win streak.
（小春）21連勝
Looks like he's back in form.
すっかり昔の勘を
取り戻したってワケね…
See, Hidaka?
おう 日高
お前に言われた通り―
I've made a full recovery after starting
over from Yie Ar Kung-Fu like you said.
｢イー･アル･カンフー｣から
やり直して完全復活したぜ…
ネオジオＣＤでの修行で
腕はもちろん―
Through my training with the Neo Geo CD,
I've elevated not only my skill,
but patience as well.
忍耐力まで
上げまくったからなー
Thanks to the load time.
ロード時間によって
Load time?
ロード時間？
Shall I repay you for the disgrace
you wrought upon me?
お前に受けた屈辱 今ここで
晴らさせてもらおうか
そして俺はもっともっと
前へ行く！
Then I'll go even further ahead.
Come on, come at me.
ホラかかってこいや
俺の超人的強さで―
I'll make you faint while coughing up
blood with my super-human ability...
吐血しながら
気絶させてやっからよ
やーだよー
I don't wanna.
What?
なぬっ！
I'm not afraid of losing...
負ける気はしないけど…
まだ矢口君の優位に
立っていたいしね
But I'd like to reign as champion
for a while longer.
That's not fair, Hidaka!
汚いぞ日高！
And by "further ahead",
you mean Ono, right?
（小春）
それに…　“前”って
大野さんのことでしょ？
Well, I felt like watching from behind
today anyway.
（小春）ま 今日はうしろで
見てたい気分だし…
（春雄）そーかい！
100連勝すっから―
That so? Then shrink in fear as I clear
a 100-win streak.
尻込みすればいいさ！
（ゲーム音声）
ぎゃ〜〜
（春雄）
あーやられた
Ah, he got me.
You're such a hard worker, Yaguchi.
（おばちゃん）
矢口君はよく働くねぇ…
Is there something you want to buy?
何か買いたいものでも
あるのー？
A Virtual Boy.
バーチャルボーイっす
Grandma's boy?
ばーちゃんぼーい？
Could it be...
（春雄）
もしかして…　あいつ
she got tired of it?
飽きたのか？
（なみえ）
ねーねー 春雄
Hey, Haruo.
夏休み一緒に映画行かない？
Want to see a movie with me over
summer break?
Haunted School?
｢学校の怪談｣
えー うん…
Uh, sure.
（春雄）
｢ザ･キング･オブ･
ファイターズ95｣も―
The King of Fighters '95 is
coming out soon
もうすぐ出るし
and I hear Tekken 2 is coming in August,
too.
｢鉄拳２｣も８月に出ると
聞く…
All these amazing games are coming out,
どんどんスゲー新作が
出てくるっていうのに
大野は何やってんだ…
what is Ono thinking?
Did something happen at home?
家で何かあったのか？
張り合いが
なくなっちまうな…
This is killing my buzz.
I mean, what have I even been doing
all this time?
っていうか
今まで俺は何やってきたんだ
"I don't have the right to face her"
合わせる顔がねーとか
ゼロからやり直すとか…
and "starting over from zero"...
Why am I just going in circles like this?
なんで俺はこうも
空回りしちまうんだろうなぁ
あ
Oh.
Young master, Yaguchi.
矢口のお坊ちゃん
Hey, it's the old man.
爺やじゃねーかよ…
It has been a long time, lad.
お久し振りでございます
お坊ちゃん
Huh? You're... alone?
ん？　１人…　なのか？
その様子を見ると
ここではないのですな…
If you're also looking for her
then she must not be here.
え？
Huh? Ono ran away?
（春雄）大野が家出！？
はい…　御家での
お嬢様に対しての躾(しつけ)が―
Yes, her discipline had become too strict
and then she ran away.
厳しくなっておりまして…
Discipline?
（春雄）躾(しつけ)…
Her curfew starts at 4 p.m.,
she was to come straight home from school.
門限は午後４時
学校が終わればほぼ直帰…
ご趣味の盛り場へ
出向くことも―
She was unable to go to the places
she enjoyed as she pleased.
ままならなくなり
お嬢様は息が詰まる日々を
過ごしておりました
The Young Miss was going through her days
with little room to breathe.
I'd worried something like this
would happen.
私もこうなるのではと
危惧(きぐ)していたのです
"Is she going to run away?
家出するんじゃないかな〜？
Oh, no, oh, no. This is bad, I'm scared."
嫌だな嫌だな
ヤバイな〜怖いな〜って…
（爺や）朝から忽然(こつぜん)と
行方知れずになり―
We suddenly lost track of her this morning
and now it's almost evening.
もう今は夕方近く…
手には何も持たず
She didn't take anything with her.
She's likely almost out of money.
おそらく所持金もわずか…
I'm going crazy worrying about her.
心配で心配で
おかしくなりそうです
高校に入ってから御友人も―
Seems she hasn't been able to make
friends since entering high school either.
お作りになっていない
ようですし…
手掛かりはお坊ちゃんだけ
だったのですが
You were the only lead I had.
お嬢様の行きそうな場所に―
Do you have any idea where she might be?
何か心当たりは
ございませんか？
Somewhere that might hold
memories for her?
お嬢様の
思い入れがあるような場所は
No, no...
（春雄）いやいや
Why does Andre's chain-link stage
come to mind?
アンドレの金網ステージが
なんで出てくんだよ
地獄じゃねえ 地獄じゃねえ
Not hell either!
I can't think of anything!
まるで思いつかねぇ…
I can only think of unrealistic places!
出てくる場所は
非現実的なものばかり…
やっぱ
アイツが行く所っていったら
The place she'd go would have to be...
近所のゲーセンは
だいたい見てみたが―
I've looked at all the neighborhood
arcades, so I doubt she's there.
いるワケねーか…
わざわざ爺やに
見つかるような所に―
She's not dumb enough to run away to
a place where the old man would find her.
家出するほど
バカじゃねぇよな…
やっぱり 修行なんてしてる
場合じゃなかった…
I guess it wasn't the time for me to be
training after all.
If I had gone to see her sooner...
もっと早くアイツに
会っていれば…
No...
いや 大野も一人で
いたいだけなのかもしれん…
Ono might just want to be alone.
動くことを
躊躇(ちゅうちょ)させられるぜ…
That makes me reluctant to look for her.
でじゃばりって
思われるかもしれねーし…
She might see me as nosy...
And it's not like I can do anything about
Ono's home situation either.
だいたい俺なんかが
大野んちの事情を―
なんとかしてやれる
ワケでもないしな…
お坊ちゃんはお嬢様の
唯一の御友人でしょお！
You are the Young Miss's only friend, lad!
Are you just going to space out and play
your Virtual Boy now that she's run away?
家でボーっと
バーチャルボーイをやってる
（春雄）まだ買ってない
まだ買ってない！
おつもりですかーっ
（ゲーム音）
Well, I've still got a couple of ideas.
（春雄）まあ まだ
思い当たるふしはある
地元からある程度離れていて
ゲーセンが多い所…
Like places further away from home
with lots of arcades.
所持金が少ないということを
考えて行ける所といったら…
A place she'd go if she didn't have much
pocket money.
KAWASAKI
ここしかない…
It'd have to be here.
一度一緒に来たことが
あるしな
We came here together once, too.
If I ran away from home,
I'd come to this town.
俺も家出するならこの町に
出向くぜ…
ゲーセンの数も
置いてある種類も―
There's a lot of arcades here with
a ton of games.
ハンパねーからな
ゲームショップも
まぁまぁある
There are plenty of game shops as well.
うほほ〜い！
Wow! I love dirty-looking shops like this!
こういう汚い感じの店は
大好物だぜ！
ニューファミコンが
あるじゃねぇか！
They have the NES!
さすが川崎！
Kawasaki delivers--
（衝撃音）
（ガイル）
春雄！
Haruo! Is that what you're here to find?
お前が捜しているものは
ソレなのか？
（春雄）ちがいます
No.
Looking for someone who may or
may not even be here
この広い街でいるかどうか
わかんねー奴を捜すのも―
in a huge town like this is reckless,
かなり無謀だが…
but I'll take it a step at a time.
地道に行くか…
I've been here enough times
川崎のゲーセンは
網羅しているからな…
置いてるゲームの種類も
なんとなく把握している
to know where everything is
and what games they have.
What is Ono feeling right now?
大野は今
どんな気分でいるかな…
家に閉じ込められた事で―
In order to release the built-up stress
of being confined at home,
溜まり溜まったものを
発散させるため
体感型ゲーム機が
多く置かれている店に―
she might've gone to an arcade with lots
of physically demanding machines.
いるかもしれん
はたまた家出した事で
ナーバスになり…
Or she could've gotten anxiety from
everything at home,
何も考えなくても出来る
and gone to a medal arcade where you don't
have to think.
メダルゲーセンにいるやも…
うぐっ
（ダルシム）
長〜く遊べるゲームを
やってるかもよ
She might be playing a game
that would last a while.
それだ！
That's it!
（春雄）
持ち金が少ない状況なら―
Without much money,
長く遊べるゲームに
すがるのは自然な行為！
it's natural she'd go for a game
with a longer duration!
俺ならそうする…！
That's what I'd do!
大野の得意な
｢ファイナルファイト｣
Ono's specialty, Final Fight.
あとは｢マジックソード｣に
｢カダッシュ｣
Or maybe Magic Sword or Cadash.
Some kind of side-scroller
is the most plausible.
横スクロールアクションが
有力だ
それらが置いていそうな
ゲーセン…
An arcade with lots of those...
まずはそこから捜してみっか
I'll try searching from there first.
あっ！
モータルコンバット２と３！
Oh! Mortal Kombat II and III!
Pistol Daimyo no Boken!
ピストル大名の大冒険！
ああ…　この脳みそを
とろけさせる世界観！
The bewitching design of this world!
Look at the show it puts on!
見よ…　このやられ姿！
大野に見せてやりてーぜ！
I want to show Ono!
（衝撃音）
（ダルシム）
春雄！
Haruo!
（春雄）ゴッ
T-This is bad.
（春雄）だっダメだ…
ついつい遊んでしまった！
I started playing without thinking.
These alluring games are trifling with me.
魅惑なゲームに
すぐ翻弄されちまう…
This is as tough as a panda trying
to ignore bamboo.
パンダが笹の葉トンネルを
素通りするくらいの―
難関っぷり…
すでに８時
It's already 8 p.m.
The town has started to shift
into nightlife.
本格的に街が夜の顔を
見せてきたぜ
The adults' time.
大人達の時間…
And with it comes danger.
そして同時に危険性も
増してくる…
Will that little princess be okay
on her own?
こんなところで
お嬢様が一人で大丈夫かな…
That is, if she's even in Kawasaki.
アイツが川崎にいればの
ハナシだけど…
I could search all night and not find her.
いくら捜しても
見つからねぇ…
She might've already gone home.
ひょっとしたら
もう家に帰ってるのかも…
ぐぐっ　落ちねぇ…
何でだよーッ！
It's not falling, why?
（頼朝）
戯れは終わりじゃ！
Playtime is over!
（衝撃音）
KAWASAKI STATION
（春雄）やめだやめ…！
I give up.
It was hopeless from the start.
初めから無謀だったんだよ…
そう今回もまた
俺の一人相撲…
That's right. I was just making
one-sided presumptions again.
As usual, a swing and a miss.
いつも通り
空振りしちまった…
（春雄）ハァ…
I want to see Ono...
（春雄）
大野と会いてーなぁ…
Haruo!
（ガイル）
春雄っ！
おう？
Huh?
（ゲームキャラ一同）
春雄ーっ！
Haruo!
-Haruo!
♪〜
GAME IN
（男Ａ）す…　すげぇな…
H-Holy crap.
She's already at 70 straight wins!
（男Ｂ）
もう70連勝にもなるぞ…
（男Ｃ）
夕方からずっとこの調子だ…
She's been going at this pace all evening.
（男Ｄ）こんなスゴイ子
川崎にいたか？
Was there a girl this strong in Kawasaki?
（男Ｅ）いや…
No way.
（男Ｆ）あっちの子は
言うまでもないが―
That Bishamon player is pretty good,
but no match for this girl.
今回のビシャモン使いも
なかなか…
（男Ｇ）うんうん
（晶）…
Jeez, your reflexes are ridiculous.
（春雄）
ったく なんつー反射神経だ
何をやってもガーキャンで
跳ね返してきやがる
No matter what I do,
it gets guard-cancelled.
You're as unbelievable as always.
相変わらずとんでもない
お嬢様だぜ
ようやっと見つけたぜ…
I've finally found you.
（晶）…
（春雄）所持金残り50円で
あの快挙を成し遂げてたのか
You managed all this with just
50 yen left?
How did you plan to pay
for the train home?
（春雄）帰りの電車賃
どーするつもりだったんだよ
飯でも食いに行くべ…
Let's get some food.
（晶）…
〜♪
（春雄）
知ってるか？　ドラクエの
１作目で姫様を助けた後に―
Did you know?
After saving the first princess
in the first Dragon Quest,
they stop at a hotel and spend the night
before returning to the castle.
お城に帰らずに宿屋に寄って
そのまま泊まるんだ
そうすっと翌朝
宿屋の主人が言うんだぜ
The next morning, the hotel owner says,
"Seems like you had a good time
last night." For real!
〝昨夜は
お楽しみでしたねぇ〞って
♪〜
Subtitle translation by
Emily Noguchi
〜♪